Our families' business status in Haicheng
الوضع التجاري لعائلاتنا في هايتشنغ
will be unmatched.
سيكون لا مثيل له.
Lu Xing.
لو شينغ.
Lu Xing, come out here!
لو شينغ، اخرج إلى هنا!
I...
أنا...
Zhu Wenjie.
تشو ون جيه.
Dad.
أب.
If Lin Mojiao hadn't told me about this,
لو لم تخبرني لين موجياو بهذا،
were you going to hide it from us forever?
هل كنت ستخفيه عنا إلى الأبد؟
That's my own business.
هذا شأني الخاص.
Why should I tell you?
لماذا عليّ أن أخبرك؟
You...
أنت...
Do you really think you can keep this child?
هل تعتقد حقاً أنك تستطيع الاحتفاظ بهذا الطفل؟
Mr. Zhu,
السيد تشو،
why can't you respect Wenjie's wishes?
لماذا لا تستطيع احترام رغبات وينجي؟
If she doesn't marry Lin Mojiao,
إذا لم تتزوج من لين موجياو،
her pregnancy
حملها
will be made public.
سيتم نشرها للعموم.
Zhu Rong and I
أنا وزو رونغ
will become the laughingstock of Haicheng.
سيصبحون أضحوكة هايتشنغ.
In your eyes,
في عينيك،
is she just a tool to protect your reputation
هل هي مجرد أداة لحماية سمعتك؟
and interests?
وما هي اهتماماتك؟
No matter who the baby's father is,
بغض النظر عن هوية والد الطفل،
as long as Wenjie wants him,
طالما أن وينجي تريده،
I'll take care of them for the rest of my life.
سأعتني بهم طوال حياتي.
Dad.
أب.
Three days later,
بعد ثلاثة أيام،
you must show up at the engagement party.
يجب عليك الحضور إلى حفل الخطوبة.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
You should go.
يجب أن تذهب.
Don't ever come back.
لا تعود أبداً.
Get out.
اخرج.
I won't leave you.
لن أتركك.
You're just in time.
لقد وصلت في الوقت المناسب تماماً.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Come on.
تعال.
Sit down and have breakfast.
اجلس وتناول الفطور.
I'm not hungry.
لست جائعاً.
Just go away.
ارحل فحسب.
Lin Mojiao has taken the initiative.
لقد أخذت لين موجياو زمام المبادرة.
Are you still going to be depressed?
هل ستظل تعاني من الاكتئاب؟
Although Vivi left,
على الرغم من رحيل فيفي،
what about Lu Xing?
ماذا عن لو شينغ؟
You won't be defeated.
لن تُهزم.
Right?
يمين؟
I quit.
لقد استقلت.
Please arrange for me.
أرجو الترتيب لي.
Lu Xing and I are leaving here.
أنا ولو شينغ سنغادر من هنا.
You can't leave now.
لا يمكنك المغادرة الآن.
You can't leave.
لا يمكنك المغادرة.
Lin Moqing, what do you mean?
لين موكينغ، ماذا تقصد؟
I've done so much for you.
لقد فعلت الكثير من أجلك.
Now I'm just asking you for a favor.
الآن أطلب منك معروفاً فقط.
You're just making excuses.
أنت تختلق الأعذار فقط.
How ungrateful you are!
يا لك من ناكر للجميل!
You can't just leave.
لا يمكنك المغادرة ببساطة.
You have to attend the engagement ceremony.
يجب عليك حضور حفل الخطوبة.
No. Are you crazy?
لا. هل أنت مجنون؟
Because only in this way,
لأنه بهذه الطريقة فقط،
can you be together forever
هل يمكنكما البقاء معاً إلى الأبد؟
without any worries.
بدون أي قلق.
Trust me.
ثق بي.
Xiao Jie will be your responsibility.
ستكون شياو جي مسؤوليتك.
Thank you all
شكراً لكم جميعاً
for coming today.
شكراً لحضوركم اليوم.
Today
اليوم
is not only an important day
إنه ليس مجرد يوم مهم
for me and Wenjie,
بالنسبة لي ولـ وينجي،
but also an important day
ولكنه أيضاً يوم مهم
for our Lin Group and Zhu Rong Group.
لمجموعتي لين وتشو رونغ.
I've prepared a gift for you.
لقد أعددت لك هدية.
You'll like it.
ستعجبك.
It's so thoughtful of Qing.
هذا تصرف لطيف للغاية من أسرة تشينغ.
I'll take it.
أنا أعتبر.
Thank you
شكرًا لك
for coming to our engagement party.
شكراً لحضوركم حفل خطوبتنا.
I'm also happy to receive your blessings.
يسعدني أيضاً أن أتلقى دعواتكم.
I went through
لقد مررت
a rough patch recently,
مررنا بفترة عصيبة مؤخراً،
but fortunately,
لكن لحسن الحظ،
Wenjie has been by my side,
لقد كانت وينجي بجانبي،
and helped me get out of the low point,
وساعدني على الخروج من تلك الحالة الصعبة،
to embrace a new life.
أن يحتضن حياة جديدة.
So,
لذا،
we will fulfill the promise
سنفي بالوعد
of the Lin and Zhu families,
من عائلتي لين وتشو،
and complete the marriage.
وإتمام الزواج.
I will marry Wenhua.
سأتزوج وينهوا.
After our engagement,
بعد خطوبتنا،
Lin Group, Blue Crane,
مجموعة لين، بلو كرين،
and Zhu Rong
وتشو رونغ
will join forces for a deep cooperation.
سنوحد جهودنا من أجل تعاون عميق.
In the future,
في المستقبل،
the business of Haicheng
أعمال هايتشنغ
will thrive.
سوف يزدهر.
A hypocrite,
منافق،
a murderer,
قاتل،
how dare he
كيف يجرؤ؟
lead Haicheng's future?
هل سيقود هايتشنغ مستقبله؟
What does that mean?
ماذا يعني ذلك؟
I...
أنا...
Lan Hewei
لان هيوي
announces here,
يعلن هنا،
after my death,
بعد وفاتي،
all my properties,
جميع ممتلكاتي،
the presidency of Lanhe Group,
رئاسة مجموعة لانهي،
and all my shares in Lanhe Group
وجميع أسهمي في مجموعة لانهي
will be transferred to Xu Meng.
سيتم نقلها إلى شو مينغ.
My husband, Lin Mojiao,
زوجي، لين موجياو،
coveted my properties.
طمع في ممتلكاتي.
On our wedding day,
في يوم زفافنا،
he forged a bribery case to frame my parents.
لقد لفّق قضية رشوة لتلفيق تهمة لوالديّ.
He also assaulted me in the abandoned tower
كما اعتدى عليّ في البرج المهجور
and pushed me off the building.
ودفعني من فوق المبنى.
That's why I was in a coma for over a year.
لهذا السبب كنت في غيبوبة لأكثر من عام.
After I woke up,
بعد أن استيقظت،
he tricked me into signing
لقد خدعني لأوقع
the resort project agreement,
اتفاقية مشروع المنتجع،
attempting to take over Blue Crane.
محاولة السيطرة على شركة بلو كرين.
With this video as evidence,
مع هذا الفيديو كدليل،
that document is null and void.
هذا المستند لاغٍ وباطل.
My property
ممتلكاتي
belongs only to Xu Meng.
هذا ملكٌ لـ Xu Meng فقط.
I was not threatened by anyone.
لم أتعرض للتهديد من أي شخص.
This video was voluntarily recorded
تم تسجيل هذا الفيديو طواعيةً
at Lin Mojiao's home.
في منزل لين موجياو.
Later on,
لاحقاً،
will be notarized by my lawyer.
سيتم توثيقها من قبل محاميّ.
You look so gentle,
تبدو لطيفاً جداً،
but you have everything you want.
لكن لديك كل ما تريد.
You are even more disgusting than I thought.
أنت أكثر إثارة للاشمئزاز مما كنت أظن.
You had plastic surgery to look like Vivi.
لقد أجريتِ عملية تجميل لتبدو مثل فيفي.
Who knows if this video was recorded by you?
من يدري إن كنت أنت من قام بتسجيل هذا الفيديو ؟
Xu Meng,
شو منغ,
have you resorted to any means
هل لجأت إلى أي وسيلة؟
to get the property of Blue Crane?
للحصول على ممتلكات بلو كرين؟
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
If that was recorded by me,
إذا كان ذلك مسجلاً من قبلي،
Then what about this?
وماذا عن هذا؟
These
هؤلاء
are all killed by you.
جميعهم قُتلوا على يديك.
It's me.
هذا أنا.
Your parents are quite smart.
والداك ذكيان للغاية.
They actually left a
لقد تركوا بالفعل
share transfer agreement that only takes effect
اتفاقية نقل الأسهم التي لا تدخل حيز التنفيذ إلا
with your signature.
مع توقيعك.
Sign it.
وقّع عليه.
I might consider letting Xu Meng go.
قد أفكر في السماح لشو مينغ بالرحيل.
This is the last thing I can do for you.
هذا آخر شيء يمكنني فعله من أجلك.
This is the evidence.
هذا هو الدليل.
You must keep it safe.
يجب عليك الحفاظ عليه في مكان آمن.
It's not like this.
الأمر ليس كذلك.
Catch him.
أمسك به.
You're a monster.
أنت وحش.
That's too much.
هذا كثير جداً.
Murderer.
قاتل.
Outrageous. Catch him.
أمرٌ شائن. يجب القبض عليه.
You're a loser.
أنت خاسر.
You're on your own.
أنت وحدك الآن.
You don't deserve any of this.
أنت لا تستحق أيًا من هذا.
So you're the one
إذن أنت هو الشخص المناسب
who will do anything for others' property.
من سيفعل أي شيء من أجل ممتلكات الآخرين.
You're just like your mother,
أنت تشبه والدتك تماماً،
a good-for-nothing.
شخص عديم الفائدة.
I'm not a good-for-nothing.
أنا لستُ شخصاً عديم الفائدة.
You're talking nonsense.
كلامك هراء.
You're just an unwanted bastard.
أنت مجرد وغد غير مرغوب فيه.
Good-for-nothing.
عديم الفائدة.
Bastard.
نذل.
You're talking nonsense.
كلامك هراء.
I'm not like them.
أنا لست مثلهم.
I'm not an illegitimate child.
أنا لست طفلاً غير شرعي.
I'll kill you.
سأقتلك.
What is he going to do?
ماذا سيفعل؟
He's killing someone.
إنه يقتل شخصاً ما.
Call the police.
اتصل بالشرطة.
Let me go.
دعني أذهب.
I'll kill you.
سأقتلك.
You deserve to die.
أنت تستحق الموت.
You all deserve to die!
جميعكم تستحقون الموت!